Guide to the Treasurer, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1717-1940; Series III
  - 1888-1901
    - Mason Brothers (*), 1888 November-1900 June (Box 177, Folder 715-718)
    - Merrill, Payson (*), 1889-1901 (Box 178, Folder 719)
    - Mills, Lyman (*), 1889-1901 (Box 178, Folder 720)
    - Morton, Bliss & Co. (*), 1894 October-1895 December (Box 178, Folder 721)
    - N, 1888 December-1901 December (Box 178, Folder 722-728)
    - Newson, H. D.
      See: box 172, folder 656
    - Newton, Hubert A. (*), 1890-1896 (Box 179, Folder 729)
    - New York Central & Hudson River Railroad Co. (*), 1890-1901 (Box 179, Folder 730)
    - New York, City of, Finance Department (*), 1889-1893 (Box 179, Folder 731)
    - Norcross Brothers (*), 1890-1894, 1900-1901 (Box 179, Folder 732)
    - O, 1889 January-1901 December (Box 179, Folder 733-735)
    - Osborn, L.E. (*), 1889-1900 (Box 179, Folder 736)
    - Osborn, Miriam A., Estate
      See: box 188, folder 830
    - P, 1889 March-1899 July (Box 179, Folder 737-740)
    - P, 1899 August - 1901 December (Box 180, Folder 741-742)
    - Peabody, Houghteling & Co. (*), 1888 October-1891 September (Box 180, Folder 743-747)
    - Peabody, Houghteling & Co. (*), 1891 October-1894 July (Box 181, Folder 748-754)
    - Peabody, Houghteling & Co. (*), 1894 August - 1896 December (Box 182, Folder 755-761)
    - Peabody, Houghteling & Co. (*), 1897 January - 1899 December (Box 183, Folder 762-769)
    - Peabody, Houghteling & Co. (*), 1900 January-1901 December (Box 184, Folder 770-775)
    - Penfield, Samuel L. (*), 1890-1900 (Box 184, Folder 776)
    - Phelps(C.P.)& Co. (*), 1898 December-1901 January (Box 184, Folder 777)
      See also: box 166, folder 593
    - Philips, Andrew W. (*), 1889-1900 August (Box 184, Folder 778-779)
    - Philips, Andrew W. (*), 1900 September-1901 December (Box 185, Folder 780)
    - Pratt & Cone (*), 1890 July-1893 March (Box 185, Folder 781)
      See also: box 165, folder 590
    - Price, Bruce (*), 1889-1891,1901 (Box 185, Folder 782)
    - Q, 1890-1900 (Box 185, Folder 783)
    - R, 1889-1901 December (Box 185, Folder 784-790)
    - Reed & Flagg (*), 1891 February - 1898 September (Box 185, Folder 791-794)
    - Richards, E. L. (*), 1889 February - 1896 December (Box 186, Folder 795)
    - Richardson (Barnum) Co. (*), 1889 May-1897 October (Box 186, Folder 796)
    - Ripley, George (*), 1899 June - 1901 December (Box 186, Folder 797)
    - Robinson, L. W. (*), 1893 May-1901 October (Box 186, Folder 798)
    - Robinson & Robinson (*), 1899 May - 1901 August (Box 186, Folder 799)
    - Rogers & Cuthbert (*), 1891 August-1901 August (Box 186, Folder 800)
    - Rogers, Cuthbert, & Ellis
      See: box 186, folder 800
    - Rowland, Williams E. (*), 1891 August - 1900 March (Box 186, Folder 801)
    - Rowse, E. S. (*), 1891 January - 1901 July (Box 186, Folder 802-803)
    - Rowse & Hopkins
      See: box 186, folders 802-803
    - Royal, Nelson
      See: box 175, folders 693-696
    - S, 1888 November - 1896 September (Box 186, Folder 804-810)
    - S, 1896 October - 1901 December (Box 187, Folder 811-817)
    - St. John, William (*), 1889-1900 (Box 187, Folder 818)
    - Sanders, F. K. (*), 1893-1901 (Box 187, Folder 819)
    - Sargent & Company (*), 1889-1901 (Box 187, Folder 820)
    - Schermerhorn, J. Maus (*), 1897 July-October (Box 187, Folder 821)
    - Schwab, J. C. (*), 1893-1901 (Box 187, Folder 822)
    - Scranton (Charles W.) Company (*), 1891-1901 (Box 187, Folder 823)
    - Scripture, E. W. (*), 1892-1901 (Box 187, Folder 824)
    - Scudder, M. L. (*), 1898-1901 (Box 187, Folder 825)
    - Second Bank of Springfield, Massachusetts, 1889 (Box 187, Folder 826)
    - Security Insurance Co. (*), 1891-1901 (Box 187, Folder 827)
    - Seaver, Jay W. (*), 1895-1901 (Box 188, Folder 828)
    - Shade and Fruit Tree Protective Association (*), 1896 (Box 188, Folder 829)
    - Shearman & Sterling (*), 1889-1896 (Box 188, Folder 830)
    - Simpson, Thacher and Brown (*), 1892-1895 (Box 188, Folder 831)
    - Sloane, Thomas G. and Estate of Thomas G. Sloane (*), 1889 May-1893 (Box 188, Folder 832)
    - Smith, Charles H. (*), 1891-1901 (Box 188, Folder 833-834)
    - Smith, Edward, 1893 (Box 188, Folder 835)
    - Smith, Herbert E. (*), 1895-1897 (Box 188, Folder 836)
    - Smith, Herbert Knox (*), 1891-1901 (Box 188, Folder 837)
    - Smith, Walter H. (*), 1891 (Box 188, Folder 838)
    - Southern New England Telephone Co. (*), 1889-1901 (Box 188, Folder 839)
    - Spencer, Trask & Co. (*), 1897-1899 (Box 188, Folder 840)
    - Sperry, N. D. (*), 1898-1901 (Box 188, Folder 841)
    - Sperry & Treat (*), 1892-1901 (Box 188, Folder 842)
    - Stanwood (E. C.) and Co. (*), 1896-1901 (Box 188, Folder 843)
    - Steinert (M.) and Sons Co. (*), 1900-1901 (Box 188, Folder 844)
    - Stevens, George Barker (*), 1888-1900 (Box 188, Folder 845)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps (*), 1898-1901 (Box 188, Folder 846-847)
    - Sweet, William E., 1901 (Box 188, Folder 848)
    - T, 1888 December-1892 December (Box 188, Folder 849-852)
    - T, 1893 January-1901 December (Box 189, Folder 853-864)
    - Tanner, S. E. (*), 1889 July-1901 August (Box 189, Folder 865)
    - Thacher, Thomas (*), 1890 June-1901 December (Box 189, Folder 866-867)
    - Thompson, C. S. (*), 1891 December-1901 August (Box 189, Folder 868)
    - Thompson, F. M. (*), 1892 April-1895 October (Box 189, Folder 869)
    - Tilson, John Q. (*), 1895 April-1901 July (Box 189, Folder 870)
    - Townsend, James M. (*), 1889 June-1901 June (Box 189, Folder 871)
    - Townsend, W. K. (*), 1890 June-1901 October (Box 189, Folder 872)
    - U, 1889 February-1901 April (Box 189, Folder 873-875)
    - United States Mortgage & Trust Co. (*), 1896 March-1901 December (Box 190, Folder 876-877)
    - United States Trust Company of New York (*), 1890 September-1901 November (Box 190, Folder 878-880)
    - V, 1890 June-1901 December (Box 190, Folder 881-882)
    - Vail, Henry West (*), 1891 September-1901 November (Box 190, Folder 883)
    - Verrill, A. E., 1894 January-1901 October (Box 190, Folder 884)
    - W, 1888 November-1895 October (Box 190, Folder 885-897)
    - W, 1895 November-1901 December (Box 191, Folder 898-909)
    - Walworth Construction and Supply Co. (*), 1893 April-1901 August (Box 191, Folder 910)
    - Warner, Charles S. (*), 1888 December-1890 April (Box 191, Folder 911)
    - Warren (H. C.) and Company (*), 1888 December-1901 December (Box 191, Folder 912-913)
    - Wayland, Francis (*), 1889 January-1901 December (Box 191, Folder 914-915)
    - Webb, Charles H. (*), 1889 February-1900 November (Box 191, Folder 916)
    - Weir, John F. (*), 1890 June-1901 October (Box 192, Folder 917-918)
    - White, A. J. (*), 1893 January-1896 October (Box 192, Folder 919)
    - Wing (Charles T.) and Co. (*), 1891 November-1894 January (Box 192, Folder 920)
    - Winslow, Lanier and Company (*), 1894 February-1899 August (Box 192, Folder 921-923)
    - Winthrop, Buchanan (*), 1889 August-1900 January (Box 192, Folder 924)
    - Wood, Irving (*), 1893 October-1896 November (Box 192, Folder 925)
    - Wright, Henry P. (*), 1890 July-1901 December (Box 192, Folder 926)
    - Y, 1889 February-1901 December (Box 192, Folder 927-928)
    - Yale Alumni Weekly (*), 1896 March-1901 December (Box 192, Folder 929)
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company (*), 1889 December-1901 December (Box 192, Folder 930)
    - Z, 1889 February-1901 September (Box 192, Folder 931)
  - 1902-1906
    - Aa-Ai (Box 193, Folder 932)
    - Al (Box 193, Folder 933)
    - Am (Box 193, Folder 934)
    - An-Ap (Box 193, Folder 935)
    - Ar-Au (Box 193, Folder 936)
    - Anderson, William G. (*), 1902 February-1906 August (Box 193, Folder 937)
    - Bab-Ban (Box 193, Folder 938)
    - Bar-Bav (Box 193, Folder 939)
    - Bea-Ben (Box 193, Folder 940)
    - Ber-Bet (Box 193, Folder 941)
    - Bi (Box 193, Folder 942)
    - Bla-Bog (Box 193, Folder 943)
    - Boi-Brau (Box 194, Folder 944)
    - Bre-Brit (Box 194, Folder 945)
    - Bro-Brow (Box 194, Folder 946)
    - Bru-But (Box 194, Folder 947)
    - Baird & Warner (*), 1902 January-1906 October (Box 194, Folder 948)
    - Baldwin, Simeon E. (*), 1902 January-1906 May (Box 194, Folder 949)
    - Bannard, Otto (*), 1902 March-1906 June (Box 194, Folder 950)
    - Barnes, Henry A. (*), 1902 February-1906 October (Box 194, Folder 951)
    - Berg, Louis DeCoppet, 1906 January-September (Box 194, Folder 952)
      See also: box 197, folder 975
    - Betts, Betts, Sheffield and Betts (*), 1902 February-1905 September (Box 194, Folder 953)
    - Bissell, Carey & Cooke (*), 1902 (Box 194, Folder 954)
    - Bissell, Carey & Cooke (*), 1903-1906 (Box 195, Folder 955-956)
    - Bristol, Stoddard, Beach & Fisher (*), 1902-1906 (Box 195, Folder 957-958)
    - Brown Brothers & Co., 1903 September-October (Box 195, Folder 959)
      See also: box 195, folder 962
    - Brown, Charles C., 1905 December-1906 June (Box 195, Folder 960)
    - Brown, Robert (*), 1902 March-1906 December (Box 195, Folder 961)
    - Brown, Thatcher (*), 1903 February-1906 June (Box 195, Folder 962)
      See also: box 195, folder 959
    - Burton (George R.) & Sons (*), 1902 January-1906 October (Box 196, Folder 963)
    - Butterworth, Frank S. (*), 1905 March-1906 October (Box 196, Folder 964)
    - Cac-Cav (Box 196, Folder 965)
    - Ce-Chat (Box 196, Folder 966)
    - Che-Chu (Box 196, Folder 967)
    - Ci-Clax (Box 196, Folder 968)
    - Cle-Clu (Box 196, Folder 969)
    - Cob-Comp (Box 196, Folder 970)
    - Con-Coop (Box 196, Folder 971)
    - Cor-Cox (Box 196, Folder 972)
    - Cra-Crut (Box 196, Folder 973)
    - Cul-Cuy (Box 196, Folder 974)
    - Cady, Berg & See (*), 1902 April-1905 January (Box 197, Folder 975)
    - Cammann (H. H.) & Co. (*), 1902 January-1906 October (Box 197, Folder 976)
    - Camp, Walter (*), 1902 May-1906 September (Box 197, Folder 977)
    - Carrère & Hastings (*), 1902 January-1906 June (Box 197, Folder 978)
    - Chapin, E. C. (*), 1903 April-1906 July (Box 197, Folder 979)
    - Chattanooga Savings Bank (*), 1902 February-1903 October (Box 197, Folder 980)
    - Chittenden, R. H. (*), 1902 January-1906 May (Box 197, Folder 981)
    - Cone, R.D. & Co. (*), 1902 January-1906 September (Box 197, Folder 982)
    - Crutcher & Welsh (*), 1902 March-1905 April (Box 198, Folder 983)
    - Curtis, Edward L. (*), 1902 May-1906 October (Box 198, Folder 984)
    - Flagg & Chambers (*), 1902 March-October (Box 198, Folder 985)
    - Da-Day (Box 198, Folder 986)
    - Dea-Dex (Box 198, Folder 987)
    - Dia-Dix (Box 198, Folder 988)
    - Doa-Doy (Box 198, Folder 989)
    - Dra-Dry (Box 198, Folder 990)
    - Du-Dy (Box 198, Folder 991)
    - Duncan, George M. (*), 1902 April-1905 July (Box 198, Folder 992)
    - Dwight, Timothy, 1902 August-1905 July (Box 198, Folder 993)
    - Ea-Ei (Box 198, Folder 994)
    - El-Em (Box 198, Folder 995)
    - En-Ew (Box 198, Folder 996)
    - Edgerton, John W. (*), 1903 December-1906 July (Box 198, Folder 997)
    - Fa-Fe (Box 199, Folder 998)
    - Fi (Box 199, Folder 999)
    - Fl (Box 199, Folder 1000)
    - Fo (Box 199, Folder 1001)
    - Fr-Fu (Box 199, Folder 1002)
    - Fidelity Trust Co. (*), 1902 April-1906 May (Box 199, Folder 1003)
    - Fisher, Irving (*), 1902 April-1906 June (Box 199, Folder 1004)
    - Fisher, Samuel
      See: box 195, folders 957-958
    - Floyd-Jones, Edward H. (*), 1902 January-1906 May (Box 199, Folder 1005)
    - French & Hollis (*), 1902 July-1904 (Box 199, Folder 1006-1007)
    - French & Hubbard (*), 1902 January-June (Box 199, Folder 1008)
    - Ga (Box 199, Folder 1009)
    - Ge (Box 199, Folder 1010)
    - Gi-Gl (Box 199, Folder 1011)
    - Go (Box 199, Folder 1012)
    - Gr (Box 200, Folder 1013)
    - Gu-Gy (Box 200, Folder 1014)
    - Gooch, F. A. (*), 1902 January-1906 October (Box 200, Folder 1015)
    - Graves, H. S. (*), 1902 January-1906 September (Box 200, Folder 1016)
    - Gregory, Herbert E. (*), 1902 February-1906 July (Box 200, Folder 1017)
    - Griswold, W. E. S. (*), 1903 January-1906 October (Box 200, Folder 1018)
    - Hac-Hal (Box 200, Folder 1019)
    - Ham-Han (Box 200, Folder 1020)
    - Harb-Harr (Box 200, Folder 1021)
    - Hart-Harv (Box 200, Folder 1022)
    - Has-Hau (Box 200, Folder 1023)
    - Haw-Haz (Box 200, Folder 1024)
    - Hea-Hen (Box 200, Folder 1025)
    - Hep-Hew (Box 200, Folder 1026)
    - Hi-Hod (Box 200, Folder 1027)
    - Hoe-Hot (Box 201, Folder 1028)
    - Hou-Hoy (Box 201, Folder 1029)
    - Hu-Hy (Box 201, Folder 1030)
    - Hadley, A. T. (*), 1903 June-1906 June (Box 201, Folder 1031)
    - Hastings & Gleason (*), 1902 September-1905 January (Box 201, Folder 1032)
    - Heaton, John Edward (*), 1902 April-1906 January (Box 201, Folder 1033)
    - Houghteling, James (*), 1902 January-1905 October (Box 201, Folder 1034)
      See also: box 206, folders 1086-1090 box 207, folders 1091-1096
    - Howells & Stokes (*), 1902 March-1903 April (Box 201, Folder 1035)
    - Hubbard, Allen
      See: box 199, folder 1008
    - I (Box 201, Folder 1036)
    - Ja (Box 201, Folder 1037)
    - Je (Box 201, Folder 1038)
    - Jo-Ju (Box 201, Folder 1039)
    - Judd, Charles H. (*), 1903 May-1906 August (Box 201, Folder 1040)
    - Ka-Ke (Box 201, Folder 1041)
    - Ki (Box 201, Folder 1042)
    - Kl-Ku (Box 201, Folder 1043)
    - Kent, William (*), 1902 January-1906 October (Box 202, Folder 1044)
    - Lab-Lan (Box 202, Folder 1045)
    - Lat-Law (Box 202, Folder 1046)
    - Le (Box 202, Folder 1047)
    - Li (Box 202, Folder 1048)
    - Lo (Box 202, Folder 1049)
    - Lu-Ly (Box 202, Folder 1050)
    - Maca-Macl (Box 202, Folder 1051)
    - Macm-Macy (Box 202, Folder 1052)
    - Mag-Man (Box 202, Folder 1053)
    - Mar-May (Box 202, Folder 1054)
    - Mea-Men (Box 202, Folder 1055)
    - Mer (Box 202, Folder 1056)
    - Mes-Mix (Box 203, Folder 1057)
    - Mob-Moo (Box 203, Folder 1058)
    - Mor (Box 203, Folder 1059)
    - Mos-My (Box 203, Folder 1060)
    - Mahoney, Martin & Cooke (*), 1904 June-1906 October (Box 203, Folder 1061)
    - Mason Brothers (*), 1901-1904 (Box 203, Folder 1062-1064)
    - Mason Brothers (*), 1905-1906 (Box 204, Folder 1065)
    - Morgan (J.P.) & Co., 1904 February-1906 September (Box 204, Folder 1066)
    - Munro, James (*), 1902-1906 (Box 204, Folder 1067-1068)
    - Na (Box 204, Folder 1069)
    - Ne (Box 204, Folder 1070)
    - Ni-Ny (Box 204, Folder 1071)
    - New Haven, City of (*), 1902-1905 (Box 204, Folder 1072)
    - New Haven, Co-W (Box 204, Folder 1073)
    - New Haven Gas Light Co. (*), 1902 January-1906 February (Box 204, Folder 1074)
    - New York, C-T (Box 204, Folder 1075)
    - New York, City of; State of, 1902-1906 (Box 205, Folder 1076)
    - New York Trust Co. (*), 1904 May-1906 October (Box 205, Folder 1077)
    - Norcross Bros. Co. (*), 1902 January-1903 July (Box 205, Folder 1078)
    - Ob-On (Box 205, Folder 1079)
    - Or-Ox (Box 205, Folder 1080)
    - Osborn, H. M. (*), 1902 January-1906 October (Box 205, Folder 1081)
    - Pa (Box 205, Folder 1082)
    - Pe (Box 205, Folder 1083)
    - Pf-Pl (Box 205, Folder 1084)
    - Po-Pu (Box 206, Folder 1085)
    - Peabody, Houghteling & Co. (*), 1901 June-1904 June (Box 206, Folder 1086-1090)
    - Peabody, Houghteling & Co. (*), 1904 July-1906 November (Box 207, Folder 1091-1096)
    - Phelps, William Lyon (*), 1902 May-1906 July (Box 208, Folder 1097)
    - Phillips, Andrew (*), 1902-1906 (Box 208, Folder 1098-1099)
    - Q (Box 208, Folder 1100)
    - Ra-Re (Box 208, Folder 1101)
    - Ri (Box 208, Folder 1102)
    - Ro-Ry (Box 208, Folder 1103)
    - Robinson, L. W. (*), 1902 January-1903 November (Box 208, Folder 1104)
    - Rogers, Cuthbert & Ellis (*), 1902 June-1905 October (Box 208, Folder 1105)
    - Rogers, Henry Wade (*), 1903 September-1906 September (Box 208, Folder 1106)
    - Rowse, E. C. (*), 1902 June-1904 December (Box 208, Folder 1107)
    - Saf-Sam (Box 208, Folder 1108)
    - San-Sch (Box 209, Folder 1109)
    - Sco-Scr (Box 209, Folder 1110)
    - Sea-Sey (Box 209, Folder 1111)
    - Sh-Sl (Box 209, Folder 1112)
    - Sme-Sn (Box 209, Folder 1113)
    - So (Box 209, Folder 1114)
    - Sp (Box 209, Folder 1115)
    - Sta (Box 209, Folder 1116)
    - Stea-Stew (Box 209, Folder 1117)
    - Sti-Sto (Box 209, Folder 1118)
    - Str-Sy (Box 209, Folder 1119)
    - Sanders, Frank K. (*), 1902 January-1905 August (Box 209, Folder 1120)
    - Simpson, Thacher, Barnum & Bartlett (*), 1902 May-1906 August (Box 210, Folder 1121)
    - Smith, Herbert E. (*), 1902 March-1906 June (Box 210, Folder 1122)
    - Smoke, Samuel A. (*), 1903 December-1906 November (Box 210, Folder 1123)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, Jr. (*), 1902-1906 (Box 210, Folder 1124-1126)
    - Ta-Te (Box 210, Folder 1127)
    - Tha-Thi (Box 210, Folder 1128)
    - Thom-Thor (Box 210, Folder 1129)
    - Ti (Box 211, Folder 1130)
    - To (Box 211, Folder 1131)
    - Tra-Tru (Box 211, Folder 1132)
    - Tu-Ty (Box 211, Folder 1133)
    - Title Guarantee & Trust Co. (*), 1905-1906 (Box 211, Folder 1134-1135)
    - U (Box 211, Folder 1136)
    - Vai-Von (Box 211, Folder 1137)
    - Wad-Wal (Box 211, Folder 1138)
    - Wan-War (Box 211, Folder 1139)
    - Was-Way (Box 212, Folder 1140)
    - Web-Wel (Box 212, Folder 1141)
    - Wes-Wey (Box 212, Folder 1142)
    - Whe-Whi (Box 212, Folder 1143)
    - Wic-Wil (Box 212, Folder 1144)
    - Win-Wor (Box 212, Folder 1145)
    - Wr-Wy (Box 212, Folder 1146)
    - Warren (H. C.) & Co. (*), 1902 January-1906 September (Box 212, Folder 1147)
    - Weir, John (*), 1902 March-1906 September (Box 212, Folder 1148)
    - Wright, Henry P. (*), 1902 January-1906 October (Box 212, Folder 1149)
    - Y (Box 213, Folder 1150)
    - Yale University Forest School (*), 1904 January-1906 February (Box 213, Folder 1151)
      See also: box 200, folder 1016
    - Yale University Law Department
      See: box 198, folder 997 box 208, folder 1106
    - Z (Box 213, Folder 1152)
    - Unidentified (Box 213, Folder 1153)
  - Filing Code
    - 3. Investments:
      - A-Bl (Box 214, Folder 1154-1161)
      - Boe-Ce (Box 215, Folder 1162-1169)
      - Cha-Ci (Box 216, Folder 1170-1176)
      - Cl-Cu (Box 217, Folder 1177-1185)
      - Da-J (Box 218, Folder 1186-1190)
      - K-Ma (Box 219, Folder 1191-1199)
      - Me-New E (Box 220, Folder 1200-1206)
      - New H-New Y (Box 221, Folder 1207-1213)
      - New York Trust Co. (Box 222, Folder 1214-1219)
      - New Y-Ph (Box 223, Folder 1220-1227)
      - Ph-Ro (Box 224, Folder 1228-1233)
      - Sa-Se (Box 225, Folder 1234-1239)
      - Sol-Ss (Box 226, Folder 1240-1245)
      - St-Tz (Box 227, Folder 1246-1250)
      - U-We (Box 228, Folder 1251-1256)
      - Wh-Z (Box 229, Folder 1257-1260)
    - 4. Peabody Museum Securities: Peabody Building Fund and Peabody General Fund, 1906 October-1915 November (Box 230, Folder 1261)
    - 5. Mortgages: New Haven and misc.
      - A-Cu (Box 230, Folder 1262-1266)
      - Do-Ma (Box 231, Folder 1267-1272)
      - Ma-Me (Box 232, Folder 1273-1275)
      - Ni-Wu (Box 233, Folder 1276-1280)
    - 5a.-d., f.-g. Mortgages: miscellaneous (Box 233, Folder 1281-1286)
    - 5m. Mortgages: miscellaneous (Box 234, Folder 1287)
    - 5n. Mortgages: New York
      - A-Hu (Box 234, Folder 1288-1292)
      - I-Ne (Box 235, Folder 1293-1299)
      - O-Ti (Box 236, Folder 1300-1305)
      - V-Z (Box 237, Folder 1306-1308)
    - 5o. Mortgages: Chicago
      - A-D (Box 237, Folder 1309-1310)
      - E-Ma (Box 238, Folder 1311-1315)
      - Me-W (Box 239, Folder 1316-1322)
    - 6. Exeter-Heald Prize, 1906 June-1911 March (Box 240, Folder 1323)
    - 7. Woolsey Hall:
      - American Ambulance Service in France motion picture: correspondence concerning benefit showing in Woolsey Hall, 1916 October-1917 March (Box 240, Folder 1324)
      - Care of, 1902 July-1917 July (Box 240, Folder 1325)
      - Engagements, 1906-1920 (Box 240, Folder 1326-1329)
      - Miscellaneous, 1912 May-1920 September (Box 240, Folder 1330)
      - Organ, maintenance and addition to, 1911 February-1918 September (Box 240, Folder 1331)
      - Stage lighting (Box 240, Folder 1332)
      - Tickets and seating arrangements (Box 240, Folder 1333)
    - 8. Downes (W. E.) Fund, 1906 November-1910 July (Box 240, Folder 1334)
    - 10. Real Estate:
      - General correspondence, 1905-1928 (Box 241, Folder 1335-1339)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1909-1921 (Box 241, Folder 1340)
      - New Haven, A-Cedar St. (Box 241, Folder 1341)
      - New Haven, Chapel St.-Elm St. (Box 242, Folder 1342-1348)
      - New Haven, Forest St.-Waterfront St. (Box 243, Folder 1349-1356)
      - New Haven, Whitney Ave.-York St. (Box 244, Folder 1357-1362)
    - 10a.-e. Real Estate: New Haven, miscellaneous (Box 245, Folder 1363-1367)
    - 11. Lewis (George H.) Property: Des Moines, Iowa, 1906 November-1915 June (Box 245, Folder 1368)
    - 12. Milner (Edwin) Gift, 1906 November (Box 245, Folder 1369)
    - 13. Dining Hall:
      - General correspondence, 1905-1916 (Box 245, Folder 1370-1371)
      - General correspondence, 1917-1925 (Box 246, Folder 1372-1376)
      - Applications for positions, 1918-1920 (Box 246, Folder 1377)
      - Applications for positions, 1921-1923 (Box 247, Folder 1378)
      - Army Mess, 1918 (Box 247, Folder 1379)
      - Committee meetings, 1911 April-1915 March (Box 247, Folder 1380)
      - Complaints against the Commonwealth Catering Corporation, 1921 July-1923 April (Box 247, Folder 1381)
      - Complaints regarding University Dining Hall, 1911-1916, 1922-1923 July (Box 247, Folder 1382-1384)
      - Dining Club constitution, 1916 March-June (Box 247, Folder 1385)
      - Information exchanged with other dining halls, 1908 November-1916 April (Box 247, Folder 1386)
      - Kellogg Service, Inc.: correspondence regarding contract for food service in University Commons, 1922 April-1923 July (Box 248, Folder 1387)
      - Students eating in, also excuses, 1923 November-1925 December (Box 248, Folder 1388)
      - Suggestions, 1911-1923 (Box 248, Folder 1389)
      - Unpaid accounts, 1908 June-1915 July (Box 248, Folder 1390)
      - Ventilation, 1909 February-1916 August (Box 248, Folder 1391)
      - Work and repairs, 1922 September-1924 December (Box 248, Folder 1392)
    - 13b. Dining Hall Plant, 1905-1908, 1912-1917 (Box 248, Folder 1393)
    - 13e. Dining Hall: Mary E. Dana claim, 1907 September-1908 August (Box 248, Folder 1394)
    - 13f. Dining Hall: alterations, 1908 July-1909 August (Box 248, Folder 1395)
    - 15. Supplies, 1917-1924 (Box 248, Folder 1396-1397)
    - 16. Psychological laboratory, 1908-1923 (Box 248, Folder 1398-1400)
    - 16a. Psychological laboratory, 1901-1907 (Box 249, Folder 1401)
    - 17. Taxes (general property), 1894-1928 (Box 249, Folder 1402-1406)
    - 17. Taxes (general property), 1929-1932 (Box 250, Folder 1407)
    - 17. Taxes (general property): conference regarding Yale contributing to the city in addition to its taxes, 1930 (Box 250, Folder 1408)
    - 17. Taxes (general property): Lapham Field House, 1923-1924 (Box 250, Folder 1409)
    - 17. Taxes (general property): miscellaneous correspondence, 1905, 1910 (Box 250, Folder 1410)
    - 18. Ordnance Stores, 1906-1907 (Box 250, Folder 1411)
    - 20. Peabody, Houghteling & Co., 1906 November-1911 April (Box 250, Folder 1412)
    - 21. Title Guarantee & Trust Co., 1906 November-1916 April (Box 250, Folder 1413)
    - 22. Civic Federation of New Haven, 1910 November-1917 July (Box 250, Folder 1414)
    - 23. Mason Brothers Northern Trust Co., 1912 October-1913 May (Box 250, Folder 1415)
    - 24. Bursar'sOffice: general correspondence, 1906-1916 (Box 250, Folder 1416-1417)
    - 24. Bursar'sOffice: general correspondence, 1917-1932 October (Box 251, Folder 1418-1425)